Presenter: At the end of twenty nineteen, Mark was still looking for Penny.
Then he found a picture on Facebook.
Mark: I wasn’t sure, but I thought it was a photo of Penny, so I messaged the woman,
and I asked: ‘Is this Penny?’.
Penny didn’t use Facebook much, so she didn’t see my message immediately.
But then she replied.
And it was her!
Penny: Mark told me for the first time what had happened at university.
I feel very sad and angry about it.
I think my father didn’t want a Black son-in-law so he told himself he was doing the right thing.
Now attitudes to race have changed a lot.
Presenter: The couple couldn’t travel to see each other at that time
because of the COVID-19 pandemic.
They waited eighteen months, and in June twenty twenty-one, Penny finally flew out to the Bahamas,
where they met again, aged sixty and sixty-one.
Mark: When we saw each other for the first time, I cried.
I couldn’t believe she was here in my arms.
Penny: I hadn’t seen him since I was nineteen,
but it was as if we’d only been apart for a year.
We hadn’t changed at all.
Presenter: After three amazing weeks with Mark, Penny came back to England.
When she returned to the Bahamas in October twenty-one,
Mark proposed to her when she got off the plane.
Now Penny is going to live in the Bahamas with him.
Penny: I feel like a whole new person.
I’ve never loved anyone the way I love Mark.
Mark: The point we met was not our time.
Now, we are looking forward to a really great future.